SEANGHAK HENG



CONTACT INFORMATION

- Svay Jrum, Khsach Kandal, Kandal
- 085290956
- Cambodian
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/seangha k-heng-34a522204/

SKILLS

- Automatic and Manual Testing
- Problem solving
- Web development
- Find bug, Technical error case, User story case

LANGUAGES

- Khmer | Native
- English | Intermediate

ABOUT ME

I am a QA tester with over 3 years of experience in software testing. During this time, I have tested software for the government(EDC, SWMA, Siem Reap government) and overseas projects I am also skilled at using automated testing tools such as Ranorex and Selenium and have some experience with web development and mobile development.

EXPERIENCE

QA TESTER

Beniten. Koh Pich, Phnom Penh | Sep 2021 - Present

My Task:

- · Create test cases and documents for testing
- . Testing follows the test case document and detects unexpected cases (Which may contain errors to ensure quality.)
- . Report bugs and errors to development teams.
- · . Communicate with developers to fix and improve production quality.
- · . Report the final result.
- . Multi-task and change from one task to another without loss of efficiency or composure.
- . Strong problem-solving and decision-making skills
- Test with Mobile App, Desktop App, and Web application

UAT

Oone Technology . Phnom Penh | 2020 - Sep 2021

My Task

- Prepare Test cases, create test cases, find bugs and add issues
- Train to frontier or review with other UAT
- Identify risks to testing and communicate with other UATs before start to add a new feature
- Do manual and automate test

EDUCATION

BACHELOR DEGREE

Royal University of Phnom Penh. | 2017 - 2021

My major is computer science at Royal University of Phnom Penh.

IEAP (INTENSIVE ENGLISH FOR ACADEMIC PURPOSES)

Pannasastra University of Cambodia. | 2019 - 2020

I studied IEAP program to improve my English skills so that I will be fully prepared to enter university and be able to study any subjects with English as the language of instruction.

TRAINING CURSE

Ant Training. | 2017 - 2018

I studied basic C/C++ and OOP, also web development at ANT Training.